Hello hello everyone welcome back to my channel
market basics in this video we are going to do
technical tips of a very remote place of insurance domain
looking at these present conditions the paste should be of
reception they will see
friends I have another motive to
make this video out of these four stocks three are
giving a very good breakup apart from that recently a lot of
benefits have been
given good commentary for the sector
that somewhere in the coming two quarters the
insurance sector cashless
1530 percent you can see that this
number is somewhere making a very good
recovery in balance of
accidents actually let's
see first of all PAC life has consolidated very well
friends
at the final 68k level it is respecting both the
lips and repeatedly searching the register
that daily hands but is in favor of 68
friends so you can comfortably take the bike go
somewhere in the images targets if you do
730 then there is an address friends for them it is a
simple project Agni Finland's
handset launch
You can easily go on its farming by bike.
SBI Life in the Next9 list is also
consolidating very well. I
definitely tried it once between 1120 and 1160, but could
not do it due to blackout.
Now Agrahari has gone, friends,
you have to ride the bike only after entering Delhi Cantt, do
not take any risk, then here for 5 minutes
because once you will see that it has caused us
loss, see if we
look at it properly from a technical point of view, what will be its image target, I can
tell you in the morning, it can go around 80,
in some upcoming temple, Agraeshwar,
one more diya, friends, one week of
31st can give a target, track which
in a text message list. ICICI
Prudential is also following its channel,
respecting it and used to take final, it is doing
great. Friends, those who are
watching this press, I can tell you somewhere that
this is of profit points and
if you are watching profit here, then we should keep it
till 720.  You can get it for free,
friends, this style will also have pressure, and
then you can go higher by doing a read test here. I am
looking at targets of 10 in the coming few days.
Tell me in the comments what your discretion is, track
balance, take it, and how are you learning
and how are you applying it. We were in our study,
last in my list, friends,
Addison is also following the download channel, you
can see now, and somewhere or the other, its
demand is approaching them, this Raj
Khatima dip, friends, is consolidating here, it is
not bringing salary, it is taking it
down somewhere, friends, no one
is starting here, by making a double border pattern,
it will give a very good free gift,
in this present scenario, friends, the recent of juice,
if I tell you that Russell
is Sonth, if not, after reversing from not, it is
closing positive above Hussain Delhi Cantt,
then you can go comfortably,
otherwise it will be negative, friends, so
aggressive investors will
get very good opposition from below,
everything about thoughts 20182, friends, you will get your
relatives  You have to send the message only after this, I will
give you one more footpath, I will tell you a little NSS so
that you can also study this and so
this tab is complete, apart from this if you
use indicators, you can check other things also,
but the thing I am telling you is
this oil is everything, okay after this
and if you find it beautiful then you can do your study,
my first tip is that you
can learn from somewhere, you will also start doing
that and you can also tell your doubts in the comment
that I am doing this again or
this pattern is being formed in this particular chart,
so sir how can we take it forward,
let's finish the video friends, I
hope that I can give you
some or the other technical tips that I can
make in Germany,
thank you for everything, please like the video,
share the video and subscribe the channel
for regular updates